MD. FAYZULLAH AMAN

WEB DEVELOPER



CONTACT

\(\) 01795504043 / 01916955766

(p) Uttor Badda, Dhaka, Bangladesh

😚 <u>fayzullahaman.bdprogrammers.com</u>

in linkedin.com/in/fayzullahaman

github.com/fayzullahaman

SKILLS

HTML, CSS, Bootstrap

JavaScript, jQuery

PHP, MySQL

WordPress

Angular

React

CodeIgniter

Laravel

Vue

ABOUT ME

Assalamu Alaikum

Nice to meet you! I have 5 years of experience as computer operator. Recently I completed web development course from IsDB-BISEW and gained experience in web development. Now I am working in web design and development. Languages I know are HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, Jquery, PHP, MySQL, WordPress, Angular, React, CodeIgniter, Laravel and Vue. I am very interested in sharing my skills in web development to the public. My passion is creating and developing a professional, beautiful website. I am committed to maintain a professional relationship with my clients and provide efficient and reliable service according to their needs. Contact me now to discuss your next project.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Computer Operator

The Royal Scintific Publication 2018 - 2022

Computer Operator

Golden Harvest 2017 - 2018

Computer Operator

Computer Graphic Design Ltd 2016 - 2017

EDUCATION

Masters

Al-Hadith & islamic Studies Islamic University 2016-2017

Honours

Al-Hadith & islamic Studies Islamic University 2012-2016

HSC/Alim

Humanities

Khamar Bari Nesaria Fazil Madrasah 2012

SSC/Dakhil

Science

Darunnazat Siddikia Kamil Madrasah 2010